Finding aid for Thomas Yoder papers, 1967-1991
Bentley Historical Library
Thomas Yoder papers
1967-1991
Bentley Historical Library
Yoder, Thomas.
89464 Aa 2
11 linear feet
462 GB (online)
Former member of the Word of God, Ann Arbor, Michigan, Catholic Pentecostal community. Reports, meeting materials, evaluations of the community's leadership, prophecies, printed materials, audiotapes of meetings, and photographs.
The Thomas Yoder papers (donor no. 5979 ) came to the library in several accessions beginning in 1977. The collection is on deposit.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Digitization: The Library has undertaken the digitization of a number of sound recordings within this collection. The resulting audio files are available for playback only in the Bentley Library Reading Room. Links to item images and additional information are available within this finding aid. Original sound recordings are only available for staff use.
The Word of God, an Ann Arbor (primarily Catholic) Pentecostal community, traces its beginnings to a small group of individuals who began to pray together regularly in November 1968. Thomas Yoder began to pray with this group in January 1968 and he quickly became an active member of the community. Yoder was very concerned with preserving the history of the group, and became the unofficial historian of the organization.
As time passed, Yoder became increasingly critical of the community's leadership. Eventually, this disagreement with the leadership, and his attempts to carry the dispute outside of the community itself, led to an understanding between Yoder and the leadership that he should terminate his public commitment to the organization. This occurred in November 1976.
The collection consists of materials accumulated by Thomas Yoder and relating to the Word of God community. The collection consists mainly of paper files, sound recordings, and videotapes.
Pentecostalism.; Photographs.; Sound recordings.; Catholic Church -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Word of God (Religious community); Yoder, Thomas.; Word of God (Religious community)
- Collected materials regarding Word of God Community
  The paper files (Collected materials regarding Word of God Community) have been arranged alphabetically by topic and include papers generated by the community itself or its members. Some of the files warrant special mention. As the Word of God community (at least during the period covered by these records) was governed by Coordinators, the Coordinator's notebooks are a valuable source of information regarding the workings of the community. These notebooks include meeting materials, decisions of the coordinators, and outlines and current policies adopted by the coordinators.
  Another excellent source is the "Word of God Archives Documents Book." This volume of documents, now in file folders and numbered, was probably used by Roberta Keene in her thesis "Formal Organization and Charisma in a Catholic Pentecostal Community" (1974). Documents in these files include summary of meetings, planning documents, reports, various statements, and memoranda.
  The Fall Conference files relate to the annual weekend gathering of the entire community. Its purpose is to allow the members to express their collective will. General Community Gatherings referred to in the files are prayer meetings held for the entire community. District Gatherings are prayer meetings of Word of God members living in a specific geographic area. Prophecies were generally given by Word of God members at prayer meetings. Within the community they were usually regarded as being divinely inspired. In recording these prophecies, Yoder relied upon the notes of others, his own notes, and audio tape recordings to reconstitute the prophecies.
  Other files include the Word of God newsletter, Community Bulletin, files relating to the Community's relationship with churches and with associated groups, such as Catholic Charismatic Renewal and the Sword of the Spirit.
  - Background / Informational (Box 1)
    - Articles, letters to the editor, etc. relating to Word of God, 1977-1987 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous articles and clippings, 1970-1988 (Box 1)
    - Articles: Acts Magazine article, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Clippings (photocopies), 1973-1990; undated (Box 1)
  - Calendar, September 1971-December 1972 (Box 1)
  - Catholic Charismatic Prayer Groups, directory, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Catholic Charismatic Renewal, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Charismatic Renewal Services catalogs, 1970-1977 (Box 1)
  - Charismatic Renewal, Materials Relating to
    - Antioch weekend manual, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Bibliography (various), undated (Box 1)
    - Campus Crusade for Christ Literature, 1965-1969 (Box 1)
    - Covenants, 1970-1975 (Box 1)
    - Statements About Charismatic Renewal, 1967-1975 (Box 1)
    - Newspaper Articles National Catholic Reporter, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Newspaper Articles Southeastern Michigan, 1969-1977 (Box 1)
    - Printed Matter, undated (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1978 (Box 1)
  - Child Care, 1973-1987; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Community Bulletin (newsletter)
    - 1972 (Box 1)
    - 1973 (Box 1)
    - 1974 (Box 1)
    - 1975 (Box 1)
    - 1976 (Box 1)
    - 1977 (Box 1)
    - 1982-1985 (Box 1)
    - 1986 (Box 1)
    - 1987 (Box 1)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 1)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Community Organization Chart, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
  - Conferences, workshops, etc.
    - General, 1968-1973 (Box 2)
    - National Conferences (Charismatic Renewal), 1970-1981 (Box 2)
    - Catholic Charismatic Renewal Conferences, 1971; 1977 (Box 2)
    - University of Steubenville, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Conference of Communities 1976, and Conference People of Praise 1975, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Coordinator's Notebook
    - Coordinator Meetings, 1972-1976 (Box 2)
    - Decisions of the Coordinators, August 1975 (Box 2)
    - Decisions of the Coordinators, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
  - Coordinator's Meeting Notes, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Coordinator's Meeting Notes, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Courses, 1969-1974 (Box 2)
  - Course: "Living as Christians in Groups", undated (Box 2)
  - Covenant: Comments on the Covenant of a Brotherhood, 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - Discipleship Dispute, circa 1975 (Box 2)
  - Duin (Julia) book chapter "Living Single ...", 1987 (Box 2)
  - Educational Programs
    - Community Weekend Manual, 1972; 1976 (Box 2)
    - Fruits of the Spirit, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
    - Living in Christian Community, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Life in the Spirit, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Married Couples, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1977 (Box 2)
  - Fall Conference
    - 1969 (Box 2)
    - 1970 (Box 2)
    - 1971 (Box 2)
    - 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - Father Charles Irvin's Editorials and Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Financial Records and Articles of Incorporation, 1971-1978 (Box 2)
  - Financial Reports
    - 1971-1974 (Box 2)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 2)
  - Finances, 1985-1989 (Box 2)
  - FIRE -- Philippines, undated (Box 2)
  - FIRE and Ralph Martin, 1984-1987 (Box 2)
  - FIRE miscellaneous, 1986; 1989 undated (Box 2)
  - Fireside Cooperative, 1977 (Box 2)
  - General Community Gatherings, 1974 (Box 2)
  - Guest House Register and Information, 1968-1974 (Box 2)
  - Handmaids, Requests for, 1972-1974 (Box 2)
  - Hispanic Missions, 1980-1987 (Box 2)
  - Homosexuality -- Desert Stream, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Human Life Center1987-1988, undated (Box 2)
  - ICO Newsletter, 1975-1976 (Box 3)
  - Information Survey (about individuals, perhaps intended for directory), 1983; 1987 (Box 3)
  - Interviews, testimonies, letters about WOG, 1975-1978 (Box 3)
  - Lamb of God (bulletins), 1988 (Box 3)
  - Leadership and Membership Directories; Dictionary of Abbreviations, 1964-1980 (Box 3)
  - Manuals
    - Leader's Manual: Lord, Teach Us to Pray, undated (Box 3)
    - WOG receptionist's manual, 1990 undated (Box 3)
    - WOG assistant administrator's manual, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
    - District secretary's manual, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Martin, Ralph
    - General, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Draft: "Face to Face With God", 1987 (Box 3)
  - Mid-west Regional Conference, 1975 (Box 3)
  - "Movement" literature, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Names, 1980-1987; undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - National Service Committee (NSC) (Box 3)
  - New Covenant, 1983-1988 (Box 3)
  - Northwest District, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
  - Other Communities and Groups
    - Lamb of God Community (Baltimore, MD), 1984-1987 (Box 3)
    - People of Hope (Newark, NJ), 1985-1986 (Box 3)
    - Bread of Life Community (Akron, OH), 1984-1986 (Box 3)
    - Christ the King Association, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Covenant Presbyterian, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Emmaus Fellowship, 1984-1988; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Lutheran Fellowship of the Word of God, 1982-1987 (Box 3)
    - Michigan Christian Association, 1983-1987 (Box 3)
    - Family Life Services, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Puebla Institute, 1984-1987 (Box 3)
    - Servants of God's Love (covenant of), undated (Box 3)
    - University Christian Outreach, 1984-1988 (Box 3)
    - Other Organizations (misc.), 1984-1987 (Box 3)
  - Outreach Programs, 1974-1977 (Box 3)
  - Pastoral Newsletter (Catholic Charismatic Renewal), 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Pastoral Renewal
    - Newsletters, 1978-1990 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1988; undated (Box 3)
    - Printed & Miscellaneous, 1983-1990 (Box 3)
  - Personal Testimonials and Membership Information Requests, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Prayer Meeting card file, including names, prayer requests, church affiliation, etc., 1969 (Box 3)
    (photocopies of index cards)
  - Prayer meeting: photocopies of photographs of Prayer Meeting, handing out of Mantles and Veils, February 1976 (Box 3)
  - Prophecies (Box 4)
    - 1967-1971 (Box 4)
    - 1972-1977 (Box 4)
    - Originals, 1967-1972 (Box 4)
  - Public Commitment, circa 1970-1975 (Box 4)
  - Report: "Report on the Catholic Pentecostal Communities in Greater Detroit", 1970 (Box 4)
  - Report: "A Report on 'The Word of God', A Charismatic Community in Ann Arbor" September 1971 (includes 1972 supplement), 1971-1972 (Box 4)
  - St. John Seminary, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
  - St. Mary's Chapel (relations with WOG), 1968-1976 (Box 4)
  - Schwager, Don: "Servants of Jesus of Christ", 1985 (Box 4)
  - Servant Books, publications by, 1985 undated (Box 4)
  - Servant Ministries, 1981-1988; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Servant Ministries newsletters, 1985-1988 (Box 4)
  - Servants of the Word (The Brotherhood), 1984-1988 (Box 4)
  - Songs of the Word of God, undated (Box 4)
  - Sword of the Spirit (Ann Arbor, MI)
    - Constitution and policy documents, 1977-1989 (Box 5)
    - Policy and Structure, 1983-1987 (Box 5)
    - Training, 1984-1987 (Box 5)
    - Newsletters, 1985-1986 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1977-1987; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Training Course, 1981-1982; undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Weddings, 1970-1975 (Box 5)
  - Witnessing, 1968-1981 (Box 5)
  - Word of God Archives Documents Book
    - Contents List 1-150, 1966-1971 (Box 5)
    - Documents No. 1-25, 1964-1969 (Box 5)
    - Documents No. 26-50, 1968-1969 (Box 5)
    - Documents No. 51-100, 1969-1971 (Box 5)
    - Documents No. 101-150, 1970-1972 (Box 5)
    - Documents, 1968-1973 (Box 5)
    - Documents, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
    - Documents, January-June 1976 (Box 5)
    - Documents, July-December 1976 (Box 5)
    - Documents, 1977 (Box 5)
  - Word of God (Box 6)
    - Guest Policies, 1983-1986 (Box 6)
    - Youth activities, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
    - Teachings from Word of God Courses, 1975 (Box 6)
    - Messages Given at Word of God "Gatherings", 1970-1983 (Box 6)
    - Letters and statements critical of Word of God leadership, 1975-1985 (Box 6)
  - Word of God Miscellaneous informational material, 1972 undated (Box 6)
  - Word of God, thesis about: Keane, Roberta Catherine, "Formal Organization and Charisma in a Catholic Pentecostal Community" Ph.D. Dissertation, University of Michigan, 1974 (Box 6)
    (photocopy taken from microfilm)
  - Yoder, Tom, Materials from and Regarding, 1971-1978 (Box 6)
  - Ypsilanti District, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence and other papers (arranged chronologically)
    - Undated, 1967-1990; 21 folders (Box 6)
- Sound Recordings
  [Digitized audio files are currently available only in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
  The Sound Recordings series consists of reel to reel and cassette audiotape recordings. Included were tapes of community anniversary celebrations, the Fall Conference, General Community Gatherings, various educational programs and inter-community conferences.
  - Audiocassette Tapes
    - Recordings of conference talks and prayer meetings, 1969-1972
      - [Prayer Meeting] Testimony of Father Anthony Delisi, 1970 September 21; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-1-1]; mp3 file; (Sermon by Father Anthony Delisi to a large congregation.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-1-2]; mp3 file; (Sermon by Father Anthony Delisi to a large congregation.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1971 January 13; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-2-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of a hymn sung by the congregation followed by a sermon.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] 2 songs, Ralph Martin, 1971 January 21; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-3-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of a prayer meeting with two hymns sung and led by Ralph Martin.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-3-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of a prayer meeting with two hymns sung and led by Ralph Martin.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] Steve Clark "Promises"; Ralph Martin, 1971 October 11, 1971 October 14, 1971 October 18; 1971 October 21; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-4-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings over several dates led by Steve Clark and Ralph Martin.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-4-2]; mp3 file; (1971 October 18, 21; A series of prayer meetings over several dates led by Steve Clark and Ralph Martin.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] (West), Jim Cavnar on "Service in the County", 1971 November 01; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-5-1]; mp3 file; (Prayer meeting led by Jim Cavnar and others entitled "Service in the County.")
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1971 November 04, 1971 November 08; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-6-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings over several dates.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-6-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings over several dates.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1971 December 03; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-7-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-7-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] Ralph Martin talk, 1971 December 16; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-8-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers interspersed with musical performances of hymns.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-8-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers interspersed with musical performances of hymns.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1971 December 20; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-9-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers interspersed with musical performances of hymns.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 January 10; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-10-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers interspersed with musical performances of hymns.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 January 17, 1972 January 20; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-11-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers interspersed with musical performances of hymns. Recorded over various dates.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-11-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers interspersed with musical performances of hymns. Recorded over various dates.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] (Hill), 1972 January 24; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-12-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers interspersed with musical performances of hymns. Also includes members of the community sharing spiritual experiences.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-12-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers interspersed with musical performances of hymns. Also includes members of the community sharing spiritual experiences.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] (South), 1972 January 24; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-13-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-13-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - Prayer Meeting; Lighthouse Album, 1972 January 27; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-14-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of hymns and Christian songs.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-14-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] General Community Gathering Ralph Martin; Talk, 1972 January 31; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-15-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers. Ralph Martin speaking.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-15-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers. Ralph Martin speaking. Hymns and music til the end of tape.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] (Hill), 1972 February 07; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-16-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers on early Christian movements.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] General Community Gathering, Bruce Yocum, 1972 February 10; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-17-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers. Bruce Yocum speaking.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 February 14; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-18-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-18-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] Hill SBC meeting, 1972 February 14; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-19-1]; mp3 file; (1) Introductory Talk, passage from Peter; Passage - John 3-1:5 [Not on tape]; 2) Talk - B - Bell.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-19-2]; mp3 file; (3) Talk. Greg Andrews; 4) Prophecy - Chris Jearline (about 1/3 way on 2nd side).)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 February 17; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-20-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-20-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] General Community Gathering Steven Clark; Talk, 1972 February 21; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-21-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers. Steve Clark talking.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-21-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers. Steve Clark talking.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 March 02; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-22-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 March 09; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-23-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] (West), 1972 March 13; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-24-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] Talk and Prophecies, 1972 March 16; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-25-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-25-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 March 20; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-26-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] - Thursday, 1972 March 23; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-27-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers. Some are identified on the cassette insert as Phil O., Jerry R., Doug G., and C.G.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] General Community Gathering, Bruce Yocum talk, 1972 March 23; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-28-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers. Bruce Yocum giving a talk.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] General Community Gathering, 1972 March 27; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-29-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] Thursday, 1972 April 06; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-30-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] C.J., 1972 April 10; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-31-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] General Community Gathering Monday, 1972 April 10; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-32-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-32-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] Thursday, 1972 April 13; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-33-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of a sermon and prayer meeting.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] Monday, 1972 April 17; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-34-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of a sermon and prayer meeting.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-34-2]; mp3 file; (Recording of a sermon and prayer meeting.)
      - [Prayer Meeting], 1972 April 24; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1], [89464-SR-35-1]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
        - [Side 2], [89464-SR-35-2]; mp3 file; (A series of prayer meetings recorded with different speakers.)
      - [Prayer Meeting] Thursday, 1972 April 27; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
        - [Side 1; no Side 2], [89464-SR-36-1]; mp3 file; (Recording of a sermon and prayer meeting.)